King Yin Pang

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING TECHNICIAN STUDENT(CURRENT)

CONTACT

Address

Markham

Phone

4372995361

E-mail

pangkingyin7899@gmail.com

TECHNICAL PROFILE

- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- PYTHON
- LINUX
- C#
- WORDPRESS
- MICROSOFT OFFICE

LANGUAGES

- CANTONESE
- ENGLISH
- MANDARIN

Early adopter of latest industry trends and strategies, resulting in consistently fresh and creative ideas.

Talented Manager with expert team leadership, planning and organizational skills built during successful career. Smoothly equip employees to independently handle daily functions and meet customer needs. Diligent trainer and mentor with exceptional management abilities and results-driven approach.

WORK HISTORY

WEB DEVELOPER, FREELACE

2022 - Current

- Provided front-end website development using WordPress, Hubspot, and other editing software.
- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX, and JSON coding.
- Coded websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery languages.
- Implemented changes and integrated requested elements to streamline business operations.
- Engaged with clients to plan and optimize site issues and queries.

MANAGER DIRECTOR, KIOTECH HK

Hong Kong | 2021 - 2022

- Decide which technical products will manufacture, how is the product packing.
- To decide the price of the product due to the cost and market value.
- Improved marketing to attract new customers and promote business.
- Developed and implemented business strategies to achieve business goals and stay competitive.
- Managed and motivated sales to keep explore potential customer.

WEB DEVELOPER, KIOTECH HK

Hong Kong | 2020 - 2021

- Provided front-end website development using WordPress, Hubspot, and other editing software.
- Implemented changes and integrated requested elements to streamline business operations.
- Engaged with clients to plan and optimize site issues and queries.

MARKETING MANAGER, CAL FNB MARKETING HK

Hong Kong |2019 - 2020

- Managing the marketing team to held each of the event
- Communicate with sales team to understand what the customer expect in the event
- Confirm event with customer and adjust the event after meeting with customer
- Solving any problem or accident when event running
- Managed workflow between staff, coordinating documents, planning, and creative material distribution.
- Help the customer created their company brand messaging, collateral materials, customer events, promotional strategies, and product commercialization
- Onboarded new employees with training and new hire documentation.

 Resolved staff member conflicts, actively listening to concerns and finding appropriate middle ground.

MARKETING ASSISTANT, CAL FNB MARKETING

Hong Kong | 2018 - 2019

- Schedule marketing event each week
- Contact different kind of blogger or internet celebrities
- Arrange event attendant list to the customer
- To integrate the report of the event, number of attendant and the benefit of the event. (Such as follower increase in social media)

SALES ADVISOR, H&M GROUP

Hong Kong | 2017 - 2018

- Increased sales by offering advice on purchases and promoting additional products.
- Maintained current knowledge of applicable sales and product changes in order to provide best possible service for all customer needs.
- Demonstrated features, answered questions and offered solutions
- Help opening and closing for the shop
- · Keep the shop looking tidy

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA - JAN 2023 - CURRENT

Centennial College of Applied Arts And Technology | Scarborough, ON Jan 2023 - Current